# **Cristina Nguyen**

San Jose, CA | 415-823-9029 | c.nguyen0994@gmail.com linkedin: cristinanguyen | github: crnguyen | medium: cristina-nguyen | portfolio: tbd

#### **SUMMARY**

A solutions-driven full stack software developer with hands-on experience in Javascript, Python, and React, and a 4 year background working as an Analyst. I have extensive experience working with various teams, a passion for learning, and I'm able to pick up new technologies quickly.

## **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

Javascript ● React ● React Native ● Express ● Node.js ● SQL ● PostgreSQL ● Postman ● Postico ● Python ● HTML ● CSS ● Postman ● Sequelize ● Django ● MongoDB ● jQuery ● Ajax ● Git ● Web Development

#### **PROJECTS**

# FoodFuse - Github - Deployed Site

Oct 2020

- Compares delivery fee and times between each service so users can make a decision on which food service to use.
- Served as Gitmaster for a group of 2; heavily involved in the UI and passing information from frontend to backend.
- Tech Stack: Django, Python, jQuery, Ajax, Javascript, Selenium, Bootstrap, HTML, CSS, Auth

## ApartMate - Github - Deployed Site

September 2020

- Users are able to login, add/claim chores and mark as complete, and invite others to their group.
- Led the frontend and design of the app in a group of 4.
- Tech Stack: MERN, Javascript, Postman, Material UI, HTML, CSS, Auth

# RecipeRec - Github - Deployed Site

August 2020

- Browse and save recipes from an API, as well as comment on a specific recipe and save it to the database.
- Developed a frontend UI and models that access the database using Sequelize and complete RESTful routes.
- Tech Stack: Javascript, Sequelize, PostgreSQL, Node.js, Express, HTML, CSS, Materialize, Auth

# Ping Pong - <u>Github</u> - <u>Deployed Site</u>

July 2020

- Rebuilt the classic game of Ping Pong for my first project, as a form of learning and practice.
- Programmed keys to have movement when pressed, and used velocity vector for ball movement.
- Tech Stack: Javascript, Canvas, HTML, CSS

## **EXPERIENCE**

## Software Engineering Immersive Fellow

July 2020 - October 2020

General Assembly | Remote - Online

Participated in a full-time Software Engineering immersive course, completing 500+ hours of projects, hackathons, and personal projects focused on real-world applications of principles and best practices.

#### **Sales Operations Analyst**

June 2018 - July 2020

Adobe | San Jose, CA

- Increased sales productivity for a team of 50 by evaluating and reporting KPI's on a weekly and monthly basis.
- Maintained Salesforce databases and created statistical Salesforce and Excel reports to visualize sales data.
- Developed quarterly metric reports to provide business insights to the Marketing and Sales teams.

## **Sales Operations Researcher**

January 2018 - June 2018

Endicia | Mountain View, CA

- Managed and maintained marketing platforms and sales databases for a team of 15.
- Streamlined the sales process by analyzing customer data and optimizing lead management to generate customer insights.

## **EDUCATION**